[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Plus was Whitney's fame simply too much for her to bear?", "question_tokens": ["Plus", "was", "Whitney", "'s", "fame", "simply", "too", "much", "for", "her", "to", "bear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "Fame in itself is an addictive drug and also fame creates an image which you cannot live up to.", "answer_tokens": ["Fame", "in", "itself", "is", "an", "addictive", "drug", "and", "also", "fame", "creates", "an", "image", "which", "you", "can", "not", "live", "up", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What did he tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "I did, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Another thing that he wanted to talk about that I asked him about, you know, that whole thing, Piers, about Mickey Fine, the pharmacist that was involved with the Michael Jackson case?", "question_tokens": ["Another", "thing", "that", "he", "wanted", "to", "talk", "about", "that", "I", "asked", "him", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "whole", "thing", ",", "Piers", ",", "about", "Mickey", "Fine", ",", "the", "pharmacist", "that", "was", "involved", "with", "the", "Michael", "Jackson", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mickey Fine", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "What do you know about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "EMON: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["EMON", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "What were you reacting to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "reacting", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Fans being robbed.", "answer_tokens": ["Fans", "being", "robbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJR", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Do you think there is any duty if you have a star of the magnitude of a Whitney Houston to give the fans something though?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "is", "any", "duty", "if", "you", "have", "a", "star", "of", "the", "magnitude", "of", "a", "Whitney", "Houston", "to", "give", "the", "fans", "something", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "I mean that's -- I mean she gave the fans something, she gave them her amazing music, her amazing voice through her records that will be there forever, the best performances of all time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "that", "'s", "--", "I", "mean", "she", "gave", "the", "fans", "something", ",", "she", "gave", "them", "her", "amazing", "music", ",", "her", "amazing", "voice", "through", "her", "records", "that", "will", "be", "there", "forever", ",", "the", "best", "performances", "of", "all", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "When did you hear the news of Whitney's death?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "of", "Whitney", "'s", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I heard it Saturday.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "heard", "it", "Saturday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What do you think -- knowing her as you do, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "--", "knowing", "her", "as", "you", "do", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "You know, I wasn't around her all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "around", "her", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "RP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "How did she seem to you, Whitney?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "she", "seem", "to", "you", ",", "Whitney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I mean, you know, when I've seen her, she's always really a very up person, she's so full of life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "I", "'ve", "seen", "her", ",", "she", "'s", "always", "really", "a", "very", "up", "person", ",", "she", "'s", "so", "full", "of", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 162, "question": "I'm sorry?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Is it right to apportion any blame or do you think --", "answer_tokens": ["Is", "it", "right", "to", "apportion", "any", "blame", "or", "do", "you", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And Chaka Khan -- could you imagine that she just would instinctively rail against anyone that tried to tell her what to do?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Chaka", "Khan", "--", "could", "you", "imagine", "that", "she", "just", "would", "instinctively", "rail", "against", "anyone", "that", "tried", "to", "tell", "her", "what", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "You know I have a feeling that she did what she wanted to do, you know, in working with her.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "have", "a", "feeling", "that", "she", "did", "what", "she", "wanted", "to", "do", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "working", "with", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "You know, it wasn't -- I mean, it was weird, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "weird", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "HOPRA: It's a very complex issue, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["HOPRA", ":", "It", "'s", "a", "very", "complex", "issue", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "I mean when they become fabulously famous, rich, successful, and they start getting into this whole drug scene, illegal and legal, do you see a change in them?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "when", "they", "become", "fabulously", "famous", ",", "rich", ",", "successful", ",", "and", "they", "start", "getting", "into", "this", "whole", "drug", "scene", ",", "illegal", "and", "legal", ",", "do", "you", "see", "a", "change", "in", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "So I don't see a lot of -- I don't usually hang out with a lot of the artists I work with, so I don't see a lot of that.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "a", "lot", "of", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "usually", "hang", "out", "with", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "artists", "I", "work", "with", ",", "so", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "a", "lot", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "How do you treat an addiction to fame?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "treat", "an", "addiction", "to", "fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "You have to realize, first of all, that fame actually causes the same brain chemical changes as a drug does.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "realize", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "that", "fame", "actually", "causes", "the", "same", "brain", "chemical", "changes", "as", "a", "drug", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Piers, I'm not at liberty to talk about that right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "at", "liberty", "to", "talk", "about", "that", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "When you worked with her, were you aware of all these struggles she was going through?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "worked", "with", "her", ",", "were", "you", "aware", "of", "all", "these", "struggles", "she", "was", "going", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I think that any singer that sings as amazing as she sung, when you have a certain pain that you can touch people, that you're carrying a pain with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "any", "singer", "that", "sings", "as", "amazing", "as", "she", "sung", ",", "when", "you", "have", "a", "certain", "pain", "that", "you", "can", "touch", "people", ",", "that", "you", "'re", "carrying", "a", "pain", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "went", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "She obviously led a very tortured life.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "obviously", "led", "a", "very", "tortured", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "But her instinctive reaction would be to rail against whatever you wanted?", "question_tokens": ["But", "her", "instinctive", "reaction", "would", "be", "to", "rail", "against", "whatever", "you", "wanted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "To take some direction, but, you know, you can't have conversations with people when they're stars about certain things.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "take", "some", "direction", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "have", "conversations", "with", "people", "when", "they", "'re", "stars", "about", "certain", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I think she was vulnerable.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "was", "vulnerable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "WRB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "How did she react to that afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "she", "react", "to", "that", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "We talked about it later, when -- the first time I visited her at her house.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "talked", "about", "it", "later", ",", "when", "--", "the", "first", "time", "I", "visited", "her", "at", "her", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "She had -- how good was her voice at its best?", "question_tokens": ["She", "had", "--", "how", "good", "was", "her", "voice", "at", "its", "best", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Better than anybody on the planet.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "than", "anybody", "on", "the", "planet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Literally?", "question_tokens": ["Literally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "For me.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Has there ever been a better recording voice?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "there", "ever", "been", "a", "better", "recording", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I always say she was the best singer ever.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "say", "she", "was", "the", "best", "singer", "ever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Do you know how she felt about it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "she", "felt", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Didn't really talk about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "really", "talk", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Was it just like the unmentionable?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "just", "like", "the", "unmentionable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "You just made a record.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "just", "made", "a", "record", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Should it be something that we focus on really, or should we celebrate -- and I sort of instinctively am beginning to feel should we focus more on these incredible songs she sang?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "it", "be", "something", "that", "we", "focus", "on", "really", ",", "or", "should", "we", "celebrate", "--", "and", "I", "sort", "of", "instinctively", "am", "beginning", "to", "feel", "should", "we", "focus", "more", "on", "these", "incredible", "songs", "she", "sang", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Israel"]}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What is your overview on what's going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "overview", "on", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Unfortunately, Iran is running terror against Israel for many, many years.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "Iran", "is", "running", "terror", "against", "Israel", "for", "many", ",", "many", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Iran"]}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Would Israel go alone?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "Israel", "go", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "HALOM: Israel is trying to stop the military program of Iran for years.", "answer_tokens": ["HALOM", ":", "Israel", "is", "trying", "to", "stop", "the", "military", "program", "of", "Iran", "for", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Has it become a problem for you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "become", "a", "problem", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Every one of us, it doesn't matter if you're Israelis, Americans, Europeans, we are in favor of those people that are asking for freedom, for human rights, for liberty.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "one", "of", "us", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "matter", "if", "you", "'re", "Israelis", ",", "Americans", ",", "Europeans", ",", "we", "are", "in", "favor", "of", "those", "people", "that", "are", "asking", "for", "freedom", ",", "for", "human", "rights", ",", "for", "liberty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]